Hello there, I'm

BRYAN FINK

Front End Web Developer

✓ Bmfink87@gmail.com



https://BryanFink.dev



git https://github.com/BryanMF87

PROFESSIONAL STATEMENT

Highly skilled and motivated frontend developer with 4+ years of experience in web development and design. Proficient in modern coding technologies and UX/ UI mocking. Demonstrated ability to work effectively in both remote and on-site environments. Strong team player with excellent communication skills.

EDUCATION

Murray State University B.A. graphic design with focus in web development May 2008 - May 2011

SKILL SET

HTML5	Bootstrap	Next JS	Figma
CSS3	SCSS	Jest	Sketch
JavaScript	React JS	GitHub	Photoshop
Tailwind	TypeScript	Figma	Illustrator

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Square, INC

Business development representative

Jan 2021 - Sept 2021

- Identified business owner challenges and interest in Square's products
- Ranked amongst top 1% of all BDRs with a 100% quota attainment rate
- · Selected for data-driven development team to create new sales technologies
- Resulted in increased sales call volume and sales efficiency

Bluegrass Book Buyers

Web developer

April 2017 - June 2020

- Created and maintained company website and online training portal.
- · Utilized Sketch, Wix, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Decreased recruit training time by 66% and increased retention by 30%
- Fully remote while multitasking several roles in a fast-paced environment

TMX Financial

Junior graphic designer

Nov 2013 - April 2014

- · Mid level company environment
- · Collaborated with web developer and design team to build digital assets
- Used Adobe creative suite
- · Worked 100% on site

Freelance work

Web developer

March 2010 - May 2011

- Created static brochure websites for local mom & pop businesses
- Used Adobe creative suite, Dreamweaver, HTML, CSS, PHP